Guide to the Juris Hartmanis papers, 1965-2008.
Hartmanis, Juris papers
- Series II. Reprints - Hartmanis
  - On the Structure of Feasible Computations, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Independence Results in Computer Science, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - On the Power of Multiplication in Random Access Machines, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - On Isomorphisms and Density of NP and Other Complete Sets, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - On Log-Tape Isomorphisms of Complete Sets, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - One-Way Log-Tape Reductions, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Quo Vadimus: Computer Science in a Decade, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - On Polynomial Time Isomorphisms of Some New Complete Sets, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Relations Between Diagonalization, Proof Systems, and Complexity Gaps, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - On the Succinctness of Different Representations of Languages, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Observations About the Development of Theoretical Computer Science, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - On Quasi-Homomorphisms and the Problem of Separating Logspace from Other Complexity Classes, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Languages Simultaneously Complete for One-Way and Two-Way Log-Tape Automata, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - A Note on Natural Complete Sets and Gödel Numberings, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Book Reviews, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - On Gödel Speed-Up and Succinctness of Language Representations, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - On Sparse sets in NP-P, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Generalized Kolmogorov Complexity and the Structure of Feasible Computations, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Computation Time of NP Sets of Different Densities, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Solvable Problems with Conflicting Relativizations, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Sparse Sets in NP-P Exptime vs. Nexptime, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Independence Results About Context-Free Languages and Lower Bounds, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Pragmatic Aspects of Complexity Theory, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - The Boolean Hierarchy I: Structural Properties, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - The Boolean Hierarchy II: Applications, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Complexity Classes Without Machines: On Complete Languages for Up, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - On Sparse Oracles Separating Feasible Complexity Classes, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - On the Importance of Being π2 - Hard, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Gödel, von Neumann, and the P = ?NP Problem, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Overview of Computational Complexity Theory, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Robust Machines Accept Easy Sets, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - New Developments in Structural Complexity, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - On IP = PSPACE and Theorems with Narrow Proofs, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Structural Complexity Theory: Recent Surprises, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - One-Way Functions and the Nonisomorphism of NP-Complete Sets, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Space Bounded Computations: Review and New Separation Results, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - On Hausdorff and Topological Dimensions of the Kolmogorov Complexity of the Real Line, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Series III. Course Materials
  - CS 381 (1), Fall 1995 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - CS 381 (2), Fall 1995 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - CS 481, Fall 1994 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - CS 280, Spring 1986 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - CS 381, Summer 1987 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - CS 381 (1), Fall 1986 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - CS 381 (2), Fall 1986 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - CS 481, Summer 1985 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - CS 481, Fall 1984 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - CS 481, Fall 1980 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - CS 481, Fall 1979 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - CS 481, Fall 1977 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - CS 481 (Course Evaluations), Fall 1976 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - CS 481, Fall 1975 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - CS 481, Fall 1974 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - CS 682, Spring 1990 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - CS 682, Spring 1987 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - CS 682, Fall 1984 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - CS 682, Spring 1985 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - CS 682, Spring 1984 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Exams, Quizzes, Homeworks (Miscellaneous), 1973-1982 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - A and Q Exams, 1974-1985 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - CS 682, Spring 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CS 682, Spring 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - CS 682, Spring 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - CS 682 (Lectures), Spring 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CS 682 (Lectures), Spring 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CS 682, Spring 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CS 682, Spring 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CS 682 (Notes), Spring 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - CS 782, Spring 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Series IV. Correspondence
  - A-B (1), 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - A-B (2), 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - C-F (1), 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - C-F (2), 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - G-J, 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - K-M (1), 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - K-M (2), 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - N-R, 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - S-T (1), 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - S-T (2), 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - U-Z, 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence With Journals, Organizations
    - Annals of Pure and Applied Logic, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - ICALP '86 and UP Paper (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - JCSS Special Editor, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence Regarding Springer Lecture Notes in Computer Science
    - Lecture Notes in Computer Science (LNCS), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Summary LNCS, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - MSRI Springer, August 1985-December 1985 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Springer Paper (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Surveys in Computer Sceince, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Surveys in Computer Science, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Other Correspondence
    - National Security Agency (NSA) Advisory, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Trip Formalities, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Theory Center Space Allocation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Series V. Lecture and Subject Files
  - Notes on the Nature of Computer Science, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Thoughts and Observations, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Li, M. and Yesha, Y. Paper, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Kazan Paper, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Bulletin Column #2 V87, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - UP Paper with Hemachandra, L., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Columbia Talk About Problems and Future of Computer Science, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Bulletin, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Program in Algorithms and Theory, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Unfettered Independence Results about Computation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Post Symposium Talk, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - One-Way Function Refs Report, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Reference, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - ICALP and TCS Paper, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Italian Lecture, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Computer Science Information, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Robusting Paper, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - References, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Gruska and IFIP, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Recruiting, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - MFCS, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Gödel Info, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Gödel Letter, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Poincare, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Gödel to Ann. History Computer Science, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - One-Way Functions; Hemachandra, L. and Hartmanis, J., 1989 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Chang, R., 1989 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Structures and SWAT and Italy, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Princeton and Rutgers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Information about University and College of Engineering, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Column Book, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Computing Research Assocation, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - CRA - Adrion Comm, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - GMD, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Hamburg Paper (1), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Hamburg Paper (2), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Traub, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Association for Computing Machinery (ACM)-Mathematical Association of America (MAA), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Hamburg Travel, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Turing and Quantum Theory Possible Column, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Real-Line Kolmogorov Paper, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - References, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Rohatgi, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Structure, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Constable, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - IFIP - Theory, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Column Book, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - National Academy of Engineering (NAE), 1992 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Series VI. Department of Computer Science Material
  - Talk About Computer Sceince at Cornell and Theory Center, October 1987 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Computer Science Department, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Computer Science Information (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Q-Exams, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Information on Computer Science Departments, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Personal Information (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Computer Science Papers, 1987-1995 (Box 21)
- Series VII. National Science Foundation (NSF) Grant Material
  - NSF Grant/Proposal Information (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - NSF Reports on Grants, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - NSF, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - NSF Grant Budget, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NSF Ext., 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - NSF Proposal, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NSF Renn., 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - NSF Grant, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Reviews and Responses, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Chang, R. - NSF, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - NSF - Japan, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - NSF Materials, 1990-1996 (Box 18)
- Series VIII. Other Professional Material
  - Chronological Conferences, Trip Information, and Talks Delivered, 2000-2005 (Box 11-12)
  - Talk and Lecture Notes, 1975-1996 (Box 12-13)
  - Chronological Conferences, Trip Information, and Talks Delivered, 1981-1996 (Box 13-14)
  - Organization, NSF Grant, and Professional Correspondence, 1989-1996 (Box 14-15)
  - Teaching and Professional Career and Awards, Including Some Biographical Information, 1992-2000 (Box 15-16)
  - Journal Editing and Submissions, 1992-1996 (Box 16-18)
  - Travel Information, 1992-2001 (Box 18)
  - Nominations, Recommendations, and Evaulations of Other Computer Scientists (Alphabetical), 1989-1997 (Box 18-19)
  - Committee, Association, and Other Organizational Duties, 1987-1997 (Box 19-20)